(Sheldon:)And I'd sooner die
than eat beans out of a can.
(Leonard:)Come on, come home with us and
tomorrow I'll take you to Legoland.
(Sheldon:)Legoland is not
the solution to everything.
(Sheldon:)And it's too much of a scene
since that movie came out.
(Leonard:)-Then what can I do?
-Leonard, I am overwhelmed.
(Sheldon:)Everything is changing
and it's simply too much.
(Sheldon:)I need to get away and think.
(Howard:)Oh, come on,
you know you're overreacting.
(Penny:)Leonard, hang on.
Just... come here for a second.
(Penny:)Maybe we need to let him go.
-What! Why?
-It might be good for him.
(Leonard:)You know he can't
take a trip like this by himself.
(Penny:)-He's a grown man.
-No, he looks like a grown man.
(Leonard:)You've seen Freaky Friday,
sometimes little kids
(Leonard:)end up in big person bodies.
(Mrs Hofstadter(on webcam):)Leonard,
we can't protect him forever.
(Leonard:)-I know, but--
-He'll be okay.